MICHAEL BENAVIDES

Chaussee de mons 816, 1070 Anderlecht · 0477934871 · Benavides.michael.munoz@gmail.com
Français (Bilingue) · Espagnol (Bilingue) · Anglais (A2)

Passionate and certified .NET developer with several years of experience in creating robust and efficient IT solutions. Always looking to learn new technologies and challenges to improve my skills.

EXPERIENCE

07/2021 - NOW

.NET DEVELOPER, NSI (ACTIRIS)

Development features on the Job Seekers' files, data like unregistering the job seeker.

Documents attestations, etc...

Development of tests for each functionality.

Refactoring of the application into services (remove mediatR and factory pattern).

Environnent: .NET Core 6, APPS72, API, swagger, Oracle DB, Oracle functions, Moq, Fluent Validation.

03/2019 - 06/2021

FULLSTACK(.NET, ANGULAR), MEGABYTE

A Guide to the Responsible Care Self-Assessment Webtool

Created a forms site to improve reporting functionality, benchmarking, improve access role security, and add multilingual functionality for the entire service.

The questionnaire is available in 18 languages.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nZeqIhi8ePg

MegaApproval

 $\label{lem:continuous} \textit{Creation of a site for the validation of invoices, with a validation flow, PDF generation.}$

Management of authorizations.

Creation of Windows services for importing accounting documents to several types of storage (local, DB, Azure Storage).

Deployment of the app on an Azure Cloud environment.

MailChimp to Sage CRM

Creation of an API that retrieves users from MailChimp, Inject into SQL DB, Implement in a frame to sage CRM.

Environnent: Azure SQL, App Service, Key Vault, Application Insights SendGrid Azure Storage, Azure AD, Azure Resource Manager .NET (core), Entity Framework (core), API, swagger, Javascript, Type Script, Angular, Angular Material, Bootstrap, ngchart2, PDFMake, SASS, html/CSS, Stored Procedure, TS-SQL

03/2019 - 06/2021

.NET DEVELOPER, CLUSTEO

Youtonomi : Dashboard admin

Development of a Web API that communicates with a connected watch and takes data from its user such as temperature, heart rate, geolocation, etc. Development of a telemonitoring website that processes the information sent by the watch and displays alarms, alerts, graphs and configurations (e.g. defining a person's threshold). Development of another module, medical record, which keeps all his medical history, e.g. diseases, vaccinations, appointments, etc.

ENVIRONMENT: ASP.NET MVC, ENTITY FRAMEWORK, LINQ, SIGNALR, BOOTSTRAP, HTML5/CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, SQL SERVER, STORED PROCEDURE, WEB API, GOOGLE CHART, NET CORE(MVC/API), ENTITY FRAMEWORK CORE, MATERIALIZE CSS, JAVASCRIPT, FULLCALENDAR, DATATABLE, ICAL.NET, ETC...

EDUCATION

2013-2020

BACHELIER EN INFORMATIQUE DE GESTION, EPHEC

2016

.NET AND SQL DATABASE, EVOLIRIS

TRAININGS

2022

EXAM AZ-900: MICROSOFT AZURE FUNDAMENTALS

2018

TRAINEE MICROSOFT INNOVATION CENTER BRUSSELS

70-483: CERTIFICATION C#

70-486: DEVELOPING ASP.NET MVC WEB APPLICATIONS

70-487: DEVELOPING MICROSOFT AZURE AND WEB SERVICE

SKILLS

- .NET Framework, .NET Core, Ling, C#, Net Core API, Swagger, Mog, FluentValidation
- Clean Architecture, CQRS
- Microsoft SQL, Ts-Sql, Oracle DB, functions
- Javascript: typescrypt, Angular, ngChart, ngxPermission
- Azure: DB, Key Vault, Application Insights SendGrid Azure Storage, Azure AD, Azure Resource Manager,
- Design: Angular Material, Bootstrap, Materialize, PDFMake, SASS, datatable, Chart (ngChart, GoogleChart), fullCalendar, Html/CSS.

SITES

- https://github.com/BenavidesMichael
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/benavides-michael-a38062a9/
- https://learn.microsoft.com/fr-fr/users/benavidesmichael/